{
    "by": "ステージ／暗室",
    "types": [
        {
            "id": "chukuippa",
            "title": "銘",
            "name": "Chukuippa",
            "message": "Let&#039;s walk with straightening your back.<br>背筋を伸ばして歩こう",
            "url": true
        },
        {
            "id": "kakitaibuki",
            "title": "記",
            "name": "Kakita Ibuki",
            "message": "Do you see the front when you look from the back?<br>ウラから覗けばオモテがみえる？",
            "url": true
        },
        {
            "id": "twontwon",
            "title": "憶",
            "name": "2n2n",
            "message": "Let&#039;s do something fun!<br>面白いことしましょ",
            "url": true
        },
        {
            "id": "yuikuroki",
            "title": "寝",
            "name": "Yui Kuroki",
            "message": "Let&#039;s enjoy Ofuton life together!<br>いっしょにおふとんライフを楽しみましょう！",
            "url": true
        },
        {
            "id": "wannabeyouth",
            "title": "靴",
            "name": "wanna be youth",
            "message": "Thank you for your hard work today.<br>今日もお疲れさまです",
            "url": true
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Well..it might be.",
            "jp": "きっとそうだろうな",
            "yes": "yes it might be",
            "left": "はい、きっと。",
            "no": "no...may be...",
            "right": "いいえ、おそらく。",
            "left_to": "Q2",
            "light_to": "Q5"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Do you want to be forgiven?",
            "jp": "許されたい？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q7",
            "light_to": "Q3"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "You like ambiguous relationship?",
            "jp": "曖昧な関係が好きだ",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q6",
            "light_to": "Q4"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Do you have a own motto/policy?",
            "jp": "あなたには座右の銘がありますか？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "ない",
            "left_to": "Q5",
            "light_to": "Q6"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "Do you like walking?",
            "jp": "歩くのは好き？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no i don't",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q6",
            "light_to": "Q8"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "Do you believe in rebirth?",
            "jp": "生まれ変わりって信じる？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q8",
            "light_to": "Q10"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Which do you believe?",
            "jp": "信じるとしたら",
            "yes": "my memory",
            "left": "自分の記憶",
            "no": "someone&#039;s memory",
            "right": "他人の記憶",
            "left_to": "Q15",
            "light_to": "Q11"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Do you predict someone&#039;s memory?",
            "jp": "他人の記憶を予想したりする？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q10",
            "light_to": "Q9"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "Do you want to exchange your motto/policy?",
            "jp": "座右の銘を交換してみたいと思いますか？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "思う",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "思わない",
            "left_to": "Q19",
            "light_to": "Q11"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "What would you do when you visit a town you don&#039;t know?",
            "jp": "知らない場所に行ったら",
            "yes": "walking around",
            "left": "町を散歩する",
            "no": "looking for a cafe",
            "right": "喫茶店を探す",
            "left_to": "Q13",
            "light_to": "Q14"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q11",
            "question": "The eyes are the windows to the soul. agree?",
            "jp": "目は口ほどに物を言う？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "そう思う",
            "no": "no i don&#039;t think so",
            "right": "そう思わない",
            "left_to": "Q14",
            "light_to": "Q12"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q12",
            "question": "Which do you rely on?",
            "jp": "どっちを頼りにする？",
            "yes": "knowledge",
            "left": "知識",
            "no": "experience",
            "right": "経験",
            "left_to": "Q13",
            "light_to": "Q16"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q13",
            "question": "Do you good at remembering directions?",
            "jp": "道を覚えるのは得意？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q15",
            "light_to": "Q16"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q14",
            "question": "Do you believe in ghost?",
            "jp": "幽霊は信じる？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q23",
            "light_to": "Q15"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q15",
            "question": "Do you often experience deja vu?",
            "jp": "普段デジャブを体験スル？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no i don't",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q18",
            "light_to": "Q19"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q16",
            "question": "What do you tend to do when you take a walk?",
            "jp": "散歩中よくすることは？",
            "yes": "listening to music",
            "left": "音楽を聴く",
            "no": "thinking about something",
            "right": "考えごと",
            "left_to": "Q17",
            "light_to": "Q19"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q17",
            "question": "What do you look at when you taking a walk?",
            "jp": "さんぽ中、つい見てしまうのは？",
            "yes": "plants at house around",
            "left": "人の家の植物",
            "no": "window of a house",
            "right": "人の家の窓",
            "left_to": "Q26",
            "light_to": "Q22"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q18",
            "question": "Is it that?",
            "jp": "あれはそれ？",
            "yes": "yes that is it",
            "left": "はい、あれはそれ。",
            "no": "no it is that",
            "right": "いいえ、それはあれ。",
            "left_to": "Q26",
            "light_to": "Q24"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q19",
            "question": "What do you think if you have to exchange your motto/policy with someone?",
            "jp": "座右の銘（もしくはモットー、ポリシー、考え、信念など）を交換せざるを得ない状況になったら、どう思いますか？",
            "yes": "would be very excited",
            "left": "ワクワクする",
            "no": "would be disappointed",
            "right": "テンションが下がる",
            "left_to": "Q20",
            "light_to": "Q23"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q20",
            "question": "What do you think if your motto/policy must be &quot;simplicity and fortitude&quot;?",
            "jp": "今日からあなたの座右の銘が「質実剛健」になったらどんな気分ですか？",
            "yes": "would be sad",
            "left": "どちらかと言えば悲しい",
            "no": "would be happy",
            "right": "どちらかと言えば嬉しい",
            "left_to": "Q21",
            "light_to": "Q22"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q21",
            "question": "simplicity and fortitude is",
            "jp": "質実剛健って",
            "yes": "difficult",
            "left": "こむずかしい",
            "no": "cool",
            "right": "かっこいい",
            "left_to": "Q24",
            "light_to": "Q25"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q22",
            "question": "The important thing should be",
            "jp": "大事なことは",
            "yes": "shared",
            "left": "共有する",
            "no": "kept a secret",
            "right": "一人で愛でる",
            "left_to": "Q26",
            "light_to": "Q23"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q23",
            "question": "A fragmentary thing is the best",
            "jp": "断片的なのが大事",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q29",
            "light_to": "Q25"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q24",
            "question": "Which would you choose?",
            "jp": "なんとなく選ぶとしたら",
            "yes": "tree",
            "left": "木 (き)",
            "no": "mountain",
            "right": "山 (やま)",
            "left_to": "Q30",
            "light_to": "Q25"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q25",
            "question": "good fortune and happiness will come to the home of those who smile",
            "jp": "笑う門には福来たる",
            "yes": "yes i think so too",
            "left": "に違いない",
            "no": "not so much..",
            "right": "とは限らない",
            "left_to": "Q30",
            "light_to": "Q31"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q26",
            "question": "What bedding do you use?",
            "jp": "いつも使う寝具は",
            "yes": "Bed",
            "left": "ベッド",
            "no": "Futon",
            "right": "敷布団",
            "left_to": "Q32",
            "light_to": "Q27"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q27",
            "question": "Which do you like?",
            "jp": "浴びるなら？",
            "yes": "sun light",
            "left": "日光",
            "no": "moon light",
            "right": "月光",
            "left_to": "Q31",
            "light_to": "Q28"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q28",
            "question": "Eventually",
            "jp": "ゆくゆくは？",
            "yes": "we will fly",
            "left": "空を飛ぶ",
            "no": "we will crawl on the ground",
            "right": "地を這う",
            "left_to": "Q29",
            "light_to": "Q34"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q29",
            "question": "Do you have a wider view?",
            "jp": "視野広い？",
            "yes": "yep",
            "left": "うん",
            "no": "nope",
            "right": "ううん",
            "left_to": "Q32",
            "light_to": "Q35"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q30",
            "question": "There is a thing that only I can see",
            "jp": "自分にしか見えないものがある",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q33",
            "light_to": "Q34"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q31",
            "question": "You would choose",
            "jp": "もし選ぶなら、",
            "yes": "Continuity is the father of success",
            "left": "継続は力なり",
            "no": "Sometimes you just have to give up",
            "right": "辞め時が肝心",
            "left_to": "Q37",
            "light_to": "Q35"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q32",
            "question": "Do you dream?",
            "jp": "よく夢を",
            "yes": "often",
            "left": "見る",
            "no": "rarely",
            "right": "見ない",
            "left_to": "Q38",
            "light_to": "Q34"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q33",
            "question": "To be honest you see the magical power?",
            "jp": "実は魔力が見える",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no i don't",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q36",
            "light_to": "Q39"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q34",
            "question": "Which would you like to be?",
            "jp": "なるとしたら",
            "yes": "a spherical object",
            "left": "球体",
            "no": "a cube",
            "right": "立方体",
            "left_to": "Q37",
            "light_to": "Q36"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q35",
            "question": "Do employees dream of a butterfly?",
            "jp": "清掃服は蝶の夢を見るか？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q41",
            "light_to": "Q38"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q36",
            "question": "Do you like human?",
            "jp": "人間は好き？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "好き",
            "no": "no i don't",
            "right": "嫌い",
            "left_to": "Q39",
            "light_to": "Q45"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q37",
            "question": "A &quot;Three years on a stone&quot; three years for me is",
            "jp": "石の上にも三年は",
            "yes": "long",
            "left": "長い",
            "no": "short",
            "right": "短い",
            "left_to": "Q43",
            "light_to": "Q40"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q38",
            "question": "Do you usually use a pillow?",
            "jp": "寝る時、枕を使う？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "使う",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "使わない",
            "left_to": "Q42",
            "light_to": "Q44"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q39",
            "question": "Things are filled with memories?",
            "jp": "思い出はモノに詰まってる？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q40",
            "light_to": "Q45"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q40",
            "question": "Does it remind you that time?",
            "jp": "それを見たらあの時を思いだす",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q48",
            "light_to": "Q43"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q41",
            "question": "Do you prefer bread to rice?",
            "jp": "パンよりお米",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "Q42",
            "light_to": "Q45"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q42",
            "question": "Delicious is happiness",
            "jp": "おいしいはしあわせ",
            "yes": "yes i think so",
            "left": "そうだね",
            "no": "no i don&#039;t think so",
            "right": "そうかな",
            "left_to": "Q47",
            "light_to": "Q49"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q43",
            "question": "You would choose",
            "jp": "もし選ぶなら、",
            "yes": "Strike while the iron is hot",
            "left": "善は急げ",
            "no": "More haste, less speed",
            "right": "急がば回れ",
            "left_to": "Q46",
            "light_to": "Q44"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q44",
            "question": "When you sleep lights are?",
            "jp": "寝る時、電気を消す？",
            "yes": "off",
            "left": "消す",
            "no": "on",
            "right": "消さない",
            "left_to": "Q49",
            "light_to": "Q50"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q45",
            "question": "Which do you prefer?",
            "jp": "選ぶならどっち？",
            "yes": "love someone",
            "left": "愛したい",
            "no": "being loved by someone",
            "right": "愛されたい",
            "left_to": "Q47",
            "light_to": "Q46"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q46",
            "question": "Which is similar to waht you want?",
            "jp": "座右の銘はどちらに近いですか？",
            "yes": "motto",
            "left": "モットー",
            "no": "policy",
            "right": "ポリシー",
            "left_to": "kakitaibuki",
            "light_to": "chukuippa"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q47",
            "question": "You feel your life is soaked in details of your daily life these days.",
            "jp": "人生が日常の細部に染み込んでいるなぁと感じる、最近",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ",
            "left_to": "twontwon",
            "light_to": "chukuippa"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q48",
            "question": "Where is memory do you think?",
            "jp": "記憶ってどこにあるの？",
            "yes": "brain/heart/body",
            "left": "脳・心・身体",
            "no": "things/space/environment",
            "right": "モノ・空間・環境",
            "left_to": "twontwon",
            "light_to": "kakitaibuki"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q49",
            "question": "Have you ever slept outdoor?",
            "jp": "屋外で寝たことある？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "ない",
            "left_to": "yuikuroki",
            "light_to": "wannabeyouth"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q50",
            "question": "Do your footprints leave?",
            "jp": "あなたの足跡は？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "残る",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "残らない",
            "left_to": "wannabeyouth",
            "light_to": "yuikuroki"
        }
    ]
}